runwayaccessories.co.uk 2016-10-22

# Privacy Policy

At Runway Accessories Limited, we are committed to maintaining your privacy. Our privacy statement is given below.

This statement may change and should be viewed regularly. Any changes made will also be notified through our newsletter and updated on our website.

Runway Accessories Limited do not sell, rent or loan any identifiable information regarding our customers to third parties without your consent.

We comply with the standards, procedures and requirements laid down in the UK Data Protection Act to ensure personal information you give us is kept secure and processed fairly and lawfully.

For our newsletter subscription, we will ask for your name and email address. Postal address, contact telephone number and date of birth are optional but may be used to tailor promotions to your requirements.

Email alerts and newsletters will be sent to inform of new products, events and special promotions from Runway Accessories Limited and the brands that they represent.

For competition entries, we will ask for your name, email address, postal address and contact telephone number. Date of birth is optional.If you do not want to receive further email alerts from Runway Accessories Limited, you can opt out by checking the box on the entry form.

If you no longer wish to receive email alerts, please simply unsubscribe from the email by clicking the unsubscribe link or send an email to our customer services department on enquiries@runwayaccessories.co.uk writing ‘unsubscribe’ in the subject heading. Alternatively you can call us on 01252 533561. You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to Runway Accessories Online, 20 Broadway studios, 2nd Floor, London, W6 7AF.

Runway Accessories Limited accept no responsibility for the content of any site to which a hyperlink from this site exists. Such links are provided for you your convenience on an ‘as is’ basis with no warranty, express or implied, for the information provided within them.

## Cookies

### What are Cookies?

Cookies are text files containing small amounts of information that allow our website to recognise your device. They are then downloaded to your device when you visit the website, if you agree to the site doing this. The cookies are then sent back to our website on each subsequent visit, or to another website that recognises that cookie.

Cookies are very useful as they allow our website to recognise your device and are widely used to make websites work more efficiently, to let you navigate between pages, to remember your preferences and to generally improve your user experience on our website. They can also help to ensure that any adverts you see online are tailored to be more relevant to you and your interests.

Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of www.runwayaccessories.co.uk. This helps us to make improvements to provide you with a better user experience when you browse our site. Some of the cookies we use are called ‘analytical cookies’; these allow us to recognise and count the number of visitors to our site, and to also see how they move around the site when they are browsing. This helps us to improve the user journey on our site, by ensuring that users are finding exactly what they are looking for.

Cookies do not contain any confidential information about our visitors, such as your home address, telephone number or credit card details. We will never share or exchange cookies with any other websites, however please note that our affiliates may also use cookies that we have no control over.

Unless you have adjusted your browser settings so that it refuses cookies, our system will issue cookies and download them onto your device when you enter our website. If you do not want to allow us to download any cookies onto your device then please adjust your settings in the Tools section of your browser.

If you don’t change your browser and continue to use our site, we will assume that you consent to us continuing to download cookies onto your device.

Whether or not you allow us to download cookies is completely up to you. However, if you choose to disable cookies by changing your browser settings our website and its features may not necessarily work in the same way or produce the same personalised experience. If you delete all of your cookies you will have to update your preferences with us again. If you use a difference device, computer profile or browser you will have to tell us your preferences again.

### Google Analytics

We use a tool called “Google Analytics” to collect information about use of this site. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit this site, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to this site. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to improve this site. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit this site, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit this site, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use and the Google Privacy Policy. You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to this site by disabling cookies on your browser.

If you have any comments or queries relating to our privacy policy, please email enquiries@runwayaccessories.co.uk  
Updated August 2016.
